<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resource>
 <item name="toc_h"><![CDATA[Contents]]></item>
 <item name="preface_h"><![CDATA[Start]]></item>
 <item name="preface_main_h"><![CDATA[Greetings Space Pilots!]]></item>
 <item name="preface_main_p"><![CDATA[Here are some useful tips to help you step up your game:<br /><br />1. Collect raw materials in space and exchange them for Credits at your space station.<br />2. Don't attack any of your company's spaceships.<br />3. Collect experience points by shooting down aliens and destroying enemy spaceships.]]></item>
 <item name="preface_ctrl_h"><![CDATA[Controls:]]></item>
 <item name="preface_ctrl_p"><![CDATA[- Mouse: Fly <br />- CTRL key: Fire lasers<br />- Space bar: Fire rockets<br />- M key: Launch a mine]]></item>
 <item name="move_h"><![CDATA[Flying on the map]]></item>
 <item name="move_main_h"><![CDATA[How can I fly?]]></item>
 <item name="move_main_p"><![CDATA[The first thing that you should practice is how to fly around the map. DarkOrbit can be played entirely with a mouse. You can send your ship to any location on the map on the screen with just one click. We recommend holding down the mouse button: It makes flying your ship much easier.]]></item>
 <item name="move_advice_h"><![CDATA[Tip]]></item>
 <item name="move_advice_p"><![CDATA[You'll spend lots of time flying around space, and sometimes you'll even have to travel long distances. That's why the mini map on the bottom right of your screen is very useful. Just click on the mini map once and your ship will fly right to the location you clicked on - even when under enemy fire. Just remember that the navigation on the mini map is relatively inaccurate in comparison to the normal map - so pay close attention to where you click.]]></item>
 <item name="attack_h"><![CDATA[Attack]]></item>
 <item name="attack_intro_h"><![CDATA[How do I attack?]]></item>
 <item name="attack_intro_p"><![CDATA[You'll often be put in dangerous situations where you have to defend yourself to survive, but what's even more common are situations where you have to carry out attacks as the attacker yourself.]]></item>
 <item name="attack_main_p"><![CDATA[There are three different categories of weapons: lasers, rockets and mines. Before you can start firing lasers and rockets, you have to pick a target first. Click your target with the left mouse button and your opponent will be marked with a red cross and their hit points will be shown. Once you've selected your target, you can select a weapon.<br /><br />If you click on <i>laser attack</i> your ship will shoot at the target until you run out of ammo, your opponent has been destroyed or you re-click <i>laser attack</i> button.<br /><br />Only one rocket will be fired for every <i>rocket attack</i> click.]]></item>
 <item name="attack_advice_h"><![CDATA[Tip]]></item>
 <item name="attack_advice_p"><![CDATA[Click on <i>laser attack</i> and then on <i>rocket attack</i> every now and then. You can also activate weapons directly by pushing the CTRL key for the laser and the space bar for the rockets.<br /><br />One more tip: Under Extras you'll find the<i>rocket booster</i>. It will fire your rockets twice as fast for you!]]></item>
 <item name="attack_mines_p"><![CDATA[The third type of weapon is the mine. Mines are kept in stock with the rockets in the cargo bay. You can launch mines by pushing the M or Y key. The mines will be activated 5 seconds after being launched, and if a space pilot comes too close to the mine, the mine will explode right in front of them. So watch your tail: If a mine explodes close to your ship, you're more than likely to sustain critical damage.]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_h"><![CDATA[Key mapping]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_attack_h"><![CDATA[Attack]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_attack_p"><![CDATA[Use your mouse to select a target. Just click on an NPC or enemy space station and your target will be locked in. Start your attack with the keyboard.<br /><br />- CTRL activates the lasers. To cancel the attack, re-click CTRL.<br />- Fire rockets with the space bar. The rockets fired are the rockets which you selected upon starting your attack. It will take some take to fire off the next rocket since the rocket launcher has to be reloaded. Rocket reloading will occur automatically.]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_laser_chg_h"><![CDATA[Changing ammo]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_laser_chg_p"><![CDATA[[1] - The 1 on the number pad is for LCB-10 ammunition (minor damage)<br />[2] - The 2 on the number pad is for MCB-25 ammunition (double damage)<br />[3] - The 3 on the number pad is for MCB-50 ammunition (triple damage)<br />[4] - The 4 on the number pad is for MCB-100 ammunition (only available in certain situations, quadruple damage)<br />[5] - The 5 on the number pad is for SAB-50 ammunition (shield absorber)]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_rocket_chg_h"><![CDATA[Changing rockets and launching mines]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_rocket_chg_p"><![CDATA[[E] - The E key is for R310 Seeker rockets (max. 1,000 damage points per rocket fired)<br />[R] - The R key is for PLT-2026 Hiob rockets (max. 2,000 damage points per rocket fired)<br />[T] - The T key is for PLT-2021 rockets (max. 4,000 damage points per rocket fired)<br />[M] or [Y] - M or Y can be used to select ACM-1 proximity mines (20% damage on detonation; only one launch per minute is possible)]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_misc_h"><![CDATA[Portal jumping, spaceship configuration and logout]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_misc_p"><![CDATA[[J] - The J key activates the portal jump to an adjacent map when you're close to the jump portal.<br />[C] - The C key switches your spaceship's setup between configuration 1 and configuration 2. After each configuration change, there is a short delay before you can switch back.<br />[L] - The L key starts the logout procedure. After the logout countdown is complete, your ship will leave the map and the star chart will close.]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_viewport_h"><![CDATA[Display setup]]></item>
 <item name="keyctrl_viewport_p"><![CDATA[[H] - The H key hides the display/control elements (HUD) on the star chart. Pushing on [H] again will make them re-appear. If the HUD is switched off, an "H" will be shown in the top left-hand corner. This indicates that you can switch the HUD back on again.<br />[B] - The B key can be used to re-activate the mini map when the HUD is hidden.<br />[F] - The F key hides bonus boxes, resources, mines and enemy cargo boxes.]]></item>
 <item name="ships_h"><![CDATA[Ships]]></item>
 <item name="ships_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I get my hands on a ship?]]></item>
 <item name="ships_get_p"><![CDATA[- You can buy a ship in the hangar. Credits will buy you normal ships and Uridium will get you <i>elite</i> ships.<br />- Or you can go to the auction at the trading post to buy ships (<i>elite</i> ships can be purchased here for Credits).]]></item>
 <item name="ships_multiple_h"><![CDATA[Can I have more than just one ship at a time?]]></item>
 <item name="ships_multiple_p"><![CDATA[No, if you buy a new ship it will replace the old one. This means that you can only have one ship to command and navigate.]]></item>
 <item name="ships_update_h"><![CDATA[What happens when I buy another ship?]]></item>
 <item name="ships_update_p"><![CDATA[Your onboard items such as weapons, ammunition, generators, extras, etc. will remain with you when you switch ships. Depending on the new ship's cargo bay and carrying capacities you might not be able to bring everything on board. If the new ship doesn't have enough room available for lasers, the extra lasers will be stored in the hangar.<br />If you buy a larger ship in the future, you can use the lasers from the hangar again.]]></item>
 <item name="ships_sell_h"><![CDATA[Can I sell or auction off ships?]]></item>
 <item name="ships_sell_p"><![CDATA[No.]]></item>
 <item name="repairs_h"><![CDATA[Repairs]]></item>
 <item name="repairs_howto_h"><![CDATA[How can I repair my ship in space?]]></item>
 <item name="repairs_howto_p"><![CDATA[As long as your ship hasn't been completely destroyed (0 HP), you can restore your hit points with a repair robot.<br />But how do you get a repair bot? <br />- Purchase them in the hangar under Extras (Credits for simple versions, Uridium for <i>elite</i> versions)<br />- Or at an auction at the trading post (<i>elite</i> versions are auctioned for Credits)<br />Once you've bought a repair bot, you'll have it forever. That is until you buy a new one, for example, for a better version. The repair robot can be used indefinitely.]]></item>
 <item name="repairs_robot_h"><![CDATA[How does the repair robot work?]]></item>
 <item name="repairs_robot_p"><![CDATA[The repair bot needs to be activated (on the star chart): Click on the <i>Robot + Extras</i> button and then on the button <i>ROB</i>. The repair robot repair your ship until all HPs have been restored. If it needs to repair something again, you'll need to reactivate it.<br />- Unwanted repair interruptions: If a ship moves or is hit, the robot will stop repairing and needs to be reactivated by clicking on <i>ROB</i>).]]></item>
 <item name="repairs_nohitpoints_h"><![CDATA[What happens if my ship has 0 HPs?]]></item>
 <item name="repairs_nohitpoints_p"><![CDATA[If the ship is completely destroyed, you can no longer travel through space and the star chart will be off limits to you.<br />You're only options are:<br />- Repair the current ship for 500 Uridium (not worth the trouble for the Phoenix Starjet, because the ship is free).<br />- Buy a new ship (see <i>How do i get a new ship?</i>. If you have a Phoenix Starjet, you should always order a new ship instead of having it repaired).]]></item>
 <item name="quests_h"><![CDATA[Missions]]></item>
 <item name="quests_main_h"><![CDATA[What are missions?]]></item>
 <item name="quests_main_p"><![CDATA[Missions require that you fulfill certain tasks.<br />These can either include jobs (special assignments), which your company needs your help completing, or challenges, where you'll have to test your skills and compete against other players.<br />After completing a job, you'll be rewarded with valuable prizes.<br /><br />Jobs which have already been completed will be counted partially and may appear again later as challenges.]]></item>
 <item name="quests_accept_h"><![CDATA[How do I accept a mission?]]></item>
 <item name="quests_accept_p"><![CDATA[Under <i>Missions</i> in the main menu, you'll find two subsections entitled <i>Jobs</i> and <i>Challenges</i>, which list all missions currently available. If you accept a job or a challenge, an additional display will appear on the space map to show you your current mission status at all times. If you accept multiple missions at once, you can select which mission should be shown in the display using the white dots on the top right. A maximum of 3 missions can be started at once.]]></item>
 <item name="quests_multiple_counting_h"><![CDATA[Do collected resources, etc. count for all missions accepted?]]></item>
 <item name="quests_multiple_counting_p"><![CDATA[No, items such as collected resources or destroyed opponents will only be counted for one mission.<br />Tip: You can see when the status of a mission, which wasn't selected, changes when its white dot in the top right flashes.]]></item>
 <item name="quests_rewards_h"><![CDATA[Do I receive rewards again for a job if I complete it as a challenge?]]></item>
 <item name="quests_rewards_p"><![CDATA[No, challenges are specifically about competing with other users and honing your own skills.]]></item>
 <item name="quests_sequence_h"><![CDATA[Does it matter in what order the subtasks are completed?]]></item>
 <item name="quests_sequence_p"><![CDATA[Certain subtasks can only be completed one after another. These subtasks are titled and numbered <i>in order</i> according to importance.<br />But that's not all: There are also missions where you only have to complete a certain number of the tasks. It's up to you to decide which tasks you'll accept.]]></item>
 <item name="quests_types_h"><![CDATA[What type of missions are there?]]></item>
 <item name="quests_types_p"><![CDATA[In order to provide you with a better overview of the different types of tasks, each mission is marked with an icon to show you what your main task will be during this mission:<br />- Destruction of enemy ships<br />- Collection of resources or discovery of new galaxies in space<br /><br />The clock icon shows you if this mission will be timed.]]></item>
 <item name="xp_h"><![CDATA[Experience points]]></item>
 <item name="xp_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I earn experience points (EP)?]]></item>
 <item name="xp_get_p"><![CDATA[- Destroy aliens (NPC)<br />- Fulfill missions: 32,000 EP per mission and more as a reward.]]></item>
 <item name="xp_effect_h"><![CDATA[What do I need experience points for?]]></item>
 <item name="xp_effect_p"><![CDATA[- Leveling up<br />Level 1: access to your company's X-1 and X-2 maps <br />Level 2: 10,000 EP, access to your company's X-3 and X-4 maps <br />Level 3: 20,000 EP, direct access from your company's X-3 map to the X-4 map <br />Level 4: 40,000 EP<br />Level 5: 80,000 EP, access to an enemy company's X-3 or X-4 maps<br />Level 6: 160,000 EP, direct access allowed from an enemy company’s X-3 map to the X-4 map<br />Level 7: 320,000 EP<br />Level 8: 640,000 EP, access to PvP maps: 4-1, 4-2, 4-3<br />Level 9: 1,280,000 EP, access to the PvP map: 4-4<br />Level 10: 2,560,000 EP, access to your company's X-5 map <br />Level 11: 5,120,000 EP, your company's X-6 map and X-7 map <br />Level 12: 10,240,000 EP, access to your company's X-8 map<br />Level 13: 20,480,000 EP, access to an enemy company's X-2 map<br />Level 14: 40,960,000 EPs, access to an enemy company's X-5 map<br />Level 15: 81,920,000 EPs, access to all enemy companies' X-6 and X-7 maps<br />Level 16: 163,840,000 EP, access to the enemy companies' X-1; you can reach the enemy space stations in the old universe<br />Level 17: 327,680,000 EP, access to all maps known to exist<br /><br />- Rank: EP is calculated 1/1,000 in the <i>Hall of Fame</i> (EP/1,000 + Honor/100); in other words, 10,000 experience points are worth 10 ranking points]]></item>
 <item name="xp_levelup_h"><![CDATA[What does leveling up do?]]></item>
 <item name="xp_levelup_p"><![CDATA[- Access to other maps: When you reach levels 2, 3, 5, 6 and 10 you will be granted access to new areas (jump portals become available), as of level 17 you will be granted access to all maps (all jump portals can be used)<br />- Access to missions: New missions are activated as your level increases.]]></item>
 <item name="honor_h"><![CDATA[Honor]]></item>
 <item name="honor_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I earn honor?]]></item>
 <item name="honor_get_p"><![CDATA[- Destroy NPCs (computer-operated alien ships)<br />- >Destroy spaces stations from other companies]]></item>
 <item name="honor_lose_h"><![CDATA[How do I lose honor?]]></item>
 <item name="honor_lose_p"><![CDATA[- You'll lose 100 honor points and 1,000 Credits by shooting down your company's space stations (blue name and selection ring).<br />- By stealing enemy cargo boxes (blue with a countdown timer)<br />(Exception: There is no deduction of honor points if your own company's space station has been outlawed, and has at least -500 honor points.)]]></item>
 <item name="honor_effect_h"><![CDATA[What do I need honor for?]]></item>
 <item name="honor_effect_p"><![CDATA[- Ranking: Honor points count 1/100 in the <i>Hall of Fame</i> with (EP/1,000 + Honor/100), e.g. 1,000 honor points are worth 10 ranking points.<br />- Better raw material prices when selling. The calculation is: Raw material price x (1 + honor points / 500,000). The maximum is the raw material price x 2 (i.e. double the sales price).<br />- In addition, negative honor also has a negative influence on the damage which you cause during an attack:<br />Honor less than -200 = 10% less damage (only 90% of the normal damage will be caused)<br />Honor less than -500 = 20% less damage (80% of the normal damage will be caused)<br />Honor less than -1000 = 40% less damage (60% of the normal damage will be caused)<br />Honor less than -2000 = 70% less damage (30% of the normal damage will be caused)<br />Honor less than -10,000 = 90% less damage (10% of the normal damage will be caused)]]></item>
 <item name="ore_h"><![CDATA[Raw materials / ores]]></item>
 <item name="ore_main_h"><![CDATA[What kind of raw materials are there?]]></item>
 <item name="ore_main_p"><![CDATA[There are seven types of raw materials:<br />-4 types of (unrefined) basic raw materials: Prometium (red), Endurium (blue), Terbium (yellow), Xenomit (silver, not available in space)<br />- 3 types of refined raw materials: Prometid (pink), Duranium (green), Promerium (yellow/orange)]]></item>
 <item name="ore_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I get raw materials?]]></item>
 <item name="ore_get_p"><![CDATA[1. Prometium, Endurium, Terbium<br />You can collect these raw materials which are floating around space and store them in the cargo bay of your ship. Just click on them and they'll be beamed into your cargo bay.<br />- Map X-1: Prometium, Endurium<br />- Map X-2: Prometium, Endurium, Terbium<br />- Map X-3 / X-4: Endurium, Terbium<br />You can also shoot down NPCs to get them:<br />- Streuner: 10 Prometium, Endurium each<br />- Lordakia: 20 Prometium, Endurium, Terbium each<br />- Saimons: 40 of each of the 3 raw materials as well as 2 Prometid and 2 Duranium<br />2. Xenomit<br />You can make a bid on Xenomit with credits or buy it right away using Uridium at the trading post.<br />You can also collect Xenomit from other players if you shoot them down and they're carrying it on board.<br />3. Prometid, Duranium, Promerium<br />Refining: You can produce these raw materials in your laboratory using the four raw materials mentioned above. The exact "recipes" can be found in the hangar under <i>Laboratory</i>.<br />You can also get Prometid, Duranium and Promerium by shooting down opponents.]]></item>
 <item name="ore_storage_h"><![CDATA[Where are the raw materials stored?]]></item>
 <item name="ore_storage_p"><![CDATA[All raw materials are put in the ship's cargo bay. A display of the stored items can be found in the Lab section. If your ship is destroyed, these raw materials can be partially lost (See above: "Destroy opponent").<br />A special item is Xenomit which can be obtained by shooting down opponents or the boss of the NPCs. Just keep in mind that this is usually easier said then done.]]></item>
 <item name="ore_purpose_h"><![CDATA[What can I do with raw materials?]]></item>
 <item name="ore_purpose_p"><![CDATA[- You can sell them for credits on your company's starbase (Map X-1): All raw materials are sold there except for Xenomit.<br />- You can refine them in the Lab section.<br />- You can upgrade weapons using refined raw materials.]]></item>
 <item name="ore_effect_h"><![CDATA[What good are refining, selling and weapons upgrades?]]></item>
 <item name="ore_effect_p"><![CDATA[- Refining reduces the necessary storage space required, because multiple units of basic raw materials are combined to make one unit of refined raw material.<br />- The profit from the sale of refined raw materials is less than the equivalent amount of unrefined raw materials.<br />- Weapon upgrades:<br />1. Prometid: One unit increases the firepower of lasers or rockets by 15% for 10 shots (up to 1,000 shots can be upgraded in advance).<br />2. Duranium: one unit increases the generator's performance or shield output by 10% for 10 minutes.<br />3. Promerium: one unit increases firepower by 30% or generator performance by 20%.]]></item>
 <item name="bounsbox_h"><![CDATA[Bonus boxes]]></item>
 <item name="bounsbox_main_h"><![CDATA[What are bonus boxes?]]></item>
 <item name="bounsbox_main_p"><![CDATA[<i>Bonus boxes</i> are small boxes that have been scattered through out outer space and contain valuable contents. <i>Bonus boxes</i> are located on all charts.]]></item>
 <item name="bounsbox_content_h"><![CDATA[What are inside the bonus boxes?]]></item>
 <item name="bounsbox_content_p"><![CDATA[The <i>bonus boxes</i> contain:<br />- Laser ammo<br />- Credits<br />- Uridium<br />- Jackpot pounds for your Jackpot<br />The amount you receive varies. Get ready for a big surprise!]]></item>
 <item name="uridium_h"><![CDATA[Uridium]]></item>
 <item name="uridium_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I get Uridium?]]></item>
 <item name="uridium_get_p"><![CDATA[- Collect <i>bonus boxes</i>: Approx. 6% contain 20, 50 or 100 Uridium<br />- Destroy NPCs<br />- Fulfill missions: Reward of 20 to 50 Uridium, for example<br />- Purchase Uridium in the hangar in <i>Credits</i>: e.g. £1.99 = 5,000 Uridium, £10 = 30,000 Uridium]]></item>
 <item name="uridium_effect_h"><![CDATA[What do I need Uridium for?]]></item>
 <item name="uridium_effect_p"><![CDATA[- For repairing a completely destroyed ship (0 HP) in the hangar for 500 Uridium, or for repairing the drones.<br />- Purchasing <i>elite</i> objects (ships, generators, weapons, ammunition, extras) in the hangar. It is also possible to bid on these items for Credits at the trading post.]]></item>
 <item name="credits_h"><![CDATA[Credits]]></item>
 <item name="credits_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I get Credits?]]></item>
 <item name="credits_get_p"><![CDATA[- <i>Collect bonus boxes</i>: A few (approx. 40%) contain amounts of 200, 500 or 1,000 credits.<br />- Shoot down NPCs.<br />- Complete missions: approx. 1,000 to 10,000 credits as a reward.<br />- Exchange Uridium in the <i>Credits</i> section: At a ratio of 1:10, e.g. 10 Uridium = 100 credits. (You should only do this in an emergency, because you can't exchange credits for Uridium.)]]></item>
 <item name="credits_effect_h"><![CDATA[What do I need Credits for?]]></item>
 <item name="credits_effect_p"><![CDATA[- You need Credits to purchase items (ships, generators, weapons, ammunition, extras) in the hangar (except for <i>elite</i> objects) or purchase items at an auction at the trading post (only <i>elite</i> objects).<br />- You need them for the clan admission (50,000 Credits), clan foundation (300,000 Credits) and for individually definable controls in the clan.]]></item>
 <item name="clan_h"><![CDATA[Clans]]></item>
 <item name="clan_main_h"><![CDATA[What is a clan?]]></item>
 <item name="clan_main_p"><![CDATA[A clan is a group of players who unite together in order to achieve certain goals. Some clans want to be big and strong, others want to get rich, etc.<br />Every clan has a so-called <i>clan tag</i> which is made up of three letters or numbers. Most of the time these tags are abbreviations.]]></item>
 <item name="clan_adv_h"><![CDATA[What are the benefits of a clan?]]></item>
 <item name="clan_adv_p"><![CDATA[A clan offers you protection since they are usually made up of many players (max. 50). A clan offers you protection in the sense that clan members can help you when you have problems (e.g. with missions. It can also distribute funds to members in need by way of tax collection.]]></item>
 <item name="clan_disadv_h"><![CDATA[What are the disadvantages of a clan?]]></item>
 <item name="clan_disadv_p"><![CDATA[There are only two disadvantages worth mentioning with a clan. First, you have to pay a predetermined tax to the clan (0 - 5%). Secondly, there's the problem that you might have to pay for the mistakes of others. If someone in the clan messes up and your clan ends up at war with other clans, then you are involved and will fight with the rest - even if you didn't really want to.<br />All for one and one for all – that's the motto in clan life. That's why you should choose a clan which you like and in which you feel comfortable.]]></item>
 <item name="dmz_h"><![CDATA[Demilitarized zones (DMZ)]]></item>
 <item name="dmz_main_h"><![CDATA[What is a DMZ?]]></item>
 <item name="dmz_main_p"><![CDATA[A DMZ is a <i>demilitarized zone</i>. That means that you can't be attacked as long as you stay inside the zone.<br />Exception:<br />If you're under attack by an opponent and fly into a DMZ, you'll continue to take damage because the attack began before you entered the zone.<br />If an enemy ship (red) enters the map, it can be attacked within the <i>DMZ</i>. As soon as you start an attack, you can also be attacked because the <i>DMZ</i> protection will end.<br /><i>DMZ</i> are only valid on your own company's maps. If you're in an enemy company's <i>DMZ</i>, you won't have any protection.]]></item>
 <item name="dmz_warning_p"><![CDATA[Note: The <i>battle maps</i> 4-1, 4-2, 4-3 and 4-4 don't have a <i>DMZ</i>. On the map 4-5, you have 15 seconds of DMZ after jumping through a gate.]]></item>
 <item name="dmz_position_h"><![CDATA[Where are the demilitarized zones?]]></item>
 <item name="dmz_position_p"><![CDATA[<i>DMZ</i> can be found at the starbase and at all jump portals on your home maps.]]></item>
 <item name="battlemaps_h"><![CDATA[Battle maps]]></item>
 <item name="battlemaps_main_h"><![CDATA[What are battle maps?]]></item>
 <item name="battlemaps_main_p"><![CDATA[The battle maps (4-1, 4-2, 4-3 and 4-4) are special PvP (Player vs. Player) maps. On these maps you'll receive 50% more experience and honor for every ship you destroy!<br />The bonus boxes on the battle maps also have 50% more contents inside them. The battle maps don't have any NAZs, which means that when you're attacked, you won't be able to escape, because the jump portal to another map won't be operational during this time.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_h"><![CDATA[Drones]]></item>
 <item name="drones_main_h"><![CDATA[What are drones?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_main_p"><![CDATA[The drones accompany your ship on the space chart and support you with extras, laser cannons and shield strength, depending on what you have available. You can decide for yourself if you want to have a battleship or if you'd prefer to play it safe and equip your ship with a higher shield strength.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I get drones?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_get_p"><![CDATA[You can purchase drones in the game under the menu item <i>Drones</i> in the hangar. The price of the drones increase with every drone sold. It doesn't make a difference if you purchase a Uridium drone or a Credit drone.<br /><br />These two types of drones vary only in design and available number of slots.<br />- The Credit drone responds to the name Flax. There is one slot free for the Flax.<br />- The Uridium drone responds to the name Iris. There are two slots free for the Iris.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_purpose_h"><![CDATA[What can I do with drones?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_purpose_p"><![CDATA[In the menu item <i>Equipment</i> in the hangar you can equip your drone with lasers, shield generators and extras. Speed generators can't be stored on drones. It would be pointless to equip drones with them since drones are purely used to escort ships. The strength of the lasers or generators increases by a certain percent with the level of your drone.]]></item>
 <item name="drones__pricelist_h"><![CDATA[How much do drones cost?]]></item>
 <item name="drones__pricelist_p"><![CDATA[The prices of the drones are as follows:<br />For the Flax:<br /> 1st drone 100,000 Credits<br /> 2nd drone 200,000 Credits<br /> 3rd drone 400,000 Credits<br /> 4th drone 800,000 Credits<br /> 5th drone 1,600,000 Credits<br /> 6th drone 3,200,000 Credits<br /> 7th drone 6,400,000 Credits<br /> 8th drone 12,800,000 Credits<br />For the Iris:<br /> 1st drone 15,000 Uridium<br /> 2nd drone 24,000 Uridium<br /> 3rd drone 42,000 Uridium<br /> 4th drone 60,000 Uridium<br /> 5th drone 84,000 Uridium<br /> 6th drone 96,000 Uridium<br /> 7th drone 126,000 Uridium<br /> 8th drone 200,000 Uridium]]></item>
 <item name="drones_repair_h"><![CDATA[What do repairs cost, and how often do I have to repair the drones?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_repair_p"><![CDATA[Repairing a drone costs 500 Uridium for a normal player, whereas a <i>Premium</i> player only has to pay 250 Uridium per drone and repair.<br />It's up to you when you want to repair your drones. The status of the destruction to the drones will be shown in %. Warning: If your drone has reached 100%, it is destroyed and you'll lose your drone for good. The degree of destruction of your drones only increases if your ship is destroyed.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_eqt_h"><![CDATA[What happens to items which are on the drones?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_eqt_p"><![CDATA[If your drone is destroyed or sold, the items will be returned to the cargo bay. You won't lose any generators, lasers or extras.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_specials_h"><![CDATA[Can I have more than 1 of the same extra?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_specials_p"><![CDATA[In a configuration you can only use one type of each extra. Using 2 repair robots or 2 Jump CPUs isn't possible. Thanks to the drone, however, you can use many different types of extras at the same time.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_level_h"><![CDATA[What is the level of the drone, and how does it increase?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_level_p"><![CDATA[The level of your drone is calculated from the experience it has collected since you've put it in use. The appearance of your drone will change according to levels, and there are 6 different levels. As the level of your drone increases, it causes more damage or the shield strength of your ship increases depending on the equipment it is carrying.<br />Remember that a drone loses one level for each time it is repaired, which means it'll have to work its way back up again afterwards.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_attack_h"><![CDATA[Do the drones shoot by themselves?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_attack_p"><![CDATA[No. Drones only shoot when you fire at an opponent; otherwise they remain inactive.]]></item>
 <item name="drones_viz_h"><![CDATA[Are my drones cloaked when I cloak my ship?]]></item>
 <item name="drones_viz_p"><![CDATA[Yes. When you cloak your ship, your drones are also cloaked.]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_h"><![CDATA[Rank insignias]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_main_h"><![CDATA[What are rank insignias?]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_main_p"><![CDATA[- Rank insignias are small graphics in front of the usernames under the ships on the charts which represent how good a particular player is according to certain criteria.]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_formula_h"><![CDATA[How are rank insignias calculated?]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_formula_p"><![CDATA[Current formula:<br />+ Experience points / 100,000<br />+ Honor points / 100<br />+ Level x 100<br />+ Number of days since registration x 6<br />+ Type of ship (<i>Phoenix</i> = 1, <i>Goliath</i> = 9) x 1,000<br />+ Shots from enemy companies' spaceships x 3<br />+ Shots from aliens / 2<br />+ Missions completed x 100<br />- shots from company members x 100<br />- shots by members of enemy companies x 4<br />- Destruction by the radiation zone x 8<br />- <i>Phoenix</i> in enemy companies shot down x 2<br />Using this formula, every user will receive a value and be compared to the other users using this value.]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_order_h"><![CDATA[What ranks are there?]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_order_p"><![CDATA[1. General (max. 1 per company)<br /> 2. Basic General (0.01%)<br /> 3. Chief Colonel (0.10%)<br /> 4. Colonel (0.50%)<br /> 5. Basic Colonel (1.00%)<br /> 6. Chief Major (1.50%)<br /> 7. Major (2.00%)<br /> 8. Basic Major (2.50%)<br /> 9. Chief Captain (3.00%)<br /> 10. Captain (3.50%)<br /> 11. Basic Captain (4.00%)<br /> 12. Chief Lieutenant (4.50%)<br /> 13. Lieutenant (5.00%)<br /> 14. Basic Lieutenant (6.00%)<br /> 15. Chief Sergeant (7.00%)<br /> 16. Sergeant (8.00%)<br /> 17. Basic Sergeant (9.00%)<br /> 18. Chief Space Pilot (10.0%)<br /> 19. Space Pilot (12.39%)<br /> 20. Basic Space Pilot (20.00%)]]></item>
 <item name="ranks_about_p"><![CDATA[This table is recalculated once daily. As the basis, this table uses all relevant figures (see calculation above) that have been achieved since the time of registration.<br /><br />Since this table varies, it may lead to fluctuations in the ranking. It's not just your own performance that counts here, but also your performance in comparison to that of the other users.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_h"><![CDATA[Jackpot Battle]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_intro_p"><![CDATA[Here is some basic information about the Jackpot battle.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_currency_purpose_h"><![CDATA[What are Jackpot pounds? And where can I find them?]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_currency_purpose_p"><![CDATA[There are jackpot pounds hidden in the bonus boxes which you can collect on the map. The pounds from these boxes will be added together and your jackpot will increase. The highest jackpot allowed is £10,000.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_winnings_p"><![CDATA[If you win a Jackpot Battle, the full amount you collected will be paid out to you in real money. The amount in your jackpot will then be reset to 0. Should you not win, your jackpot total will remain unchanged, and you will be able to continue collecting until the next Jackpot Battle.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_main_h"><![CDATA[What is the Jackpot battle?]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_main_p"><![CDATA[There is a Jackpot Battle on the second Sunday of every month. All players having reached the age of 18 may participate in these battles. Players who have been destroyed cannot return to this map.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_winner_p"><![CDATA[The total amount in the winner's jackpot will be paid out to the winner in real GBPs. Should the amount collected be zero, the winner will receive nothing. The winnings will be transferred to the winner's bank account by direct transfer. This is why the players are asked to enter their bank information upon registration.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_participate_h"><![CDATA[How can I compete in the Jackpot Battle? When does it take place?]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_participate_p"><![CDATA[Three days before the Jackpot Battle, an invitation (event) layer will be displayed. You can enter your information in this layer in order to participate in the battle. Registration for the Jackpot Battle closes at 1:30pm on the day of the battle. At 2:00pm, on the day of the battle, all registered participants are placed on the battle map whether they are online or not.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_pre_procedure_p"><![CDATA[At 2:10pm, all participants are on the battle map and the attack ban will be lifted, then the battle can begin.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_procedure_p"><![CDATA[The battle map is split up into many different sub-maps. Five hundred players are randomly assigned to each sub-map. Should only 500 players remain, these players will be assigned to one final map, and the showdown will take place on this map. The Jackpot Battle ends at 10:00pm. If more than one player remains at this time, a draw will decide the winner.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_post_procedure_p"><![CDATA[As soon as the battle is over for you, your spaceship will be transported back to the X-1 map, regardless of where it was before the battle.]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_age_limit_h"><![CDATA[Is there an age limit?]]></item>
 <item name="jpbattle_age_limit_p"><![CDATA[To participate in and/or collect the winnings of a Jackpot Battle, you must have reached the age of 18. Minors (players under 18 years old) are not allowed to participate in or collect winnings from the Jackpot Battle due to legal reasons. This also applies to minors who have their parents'/legal guardian's permission. Before any prizes are awarded, the age of all participants will be verified. Should it become clear upon verification that the birth date provided by the winner is false, the winner will lose all claim and entitlement to the prize money.]]></item>
 <item name="noobprotection_h"><![CDATA[Newbie protection]]></item>
 <item name="noobprotection_main_h"><![CDATA[What is newbie protection?]]></item>
 <item name="noobprotection_main_p"><![CDATA[This protection is divided into two categories:<br /> - On the X-1 start charts, every user up to level 6 will see their opponents on the mini map marked with an orange square. Only users from enemy companies will be shown with these squares. An NPC will continue to be displayed as usual.<br /> - On the X-1 and X-2 maps all users have a danger display. This is located on the right side of the mini map. If a member of an enemy company jumps onto your map, the danger display will appear. That way you can always know how dangerous it is on your map.]]></item>
 <item name="noobprotection_appendix_p"><![CDATA[The display of enemies in orange boxes is only available on the X-1 maps. The system which displays enemies on X-1 in orange is only available up to level 6. The danger display on X-1 and X-2 is independent of the level.]]></item>
 <item name="titles_h"><![CDATA[Title system]]></item>
 <item name="titles_main_h"><![CDATA[What is a title?]]></item>
 <item name="titles_main_p"><![CDATA[A title is an award for the user. In addition to the names, rank insignias and company affiliation, this title will also be displayed on the star chart in yellow above the names. There are 10 titles to start with, but from time to time new titles will be added. You can make suggestions about the titles in the corresponding threads and current discussions in the forum.]]></item>
 <item name="titles_examples_h"><![CDATA[What titles are there?]]></item>
 <item name="titles_examples_p"><![CDATA[For example, you could be Master of the Orbit, Emperor, Goli Hunter, Alien Hunter ...]]></item>
 <item name="titles_quantity_h"><![CDATA[How many of this title are there?]]></item>
 <item name="titles_quantity_p"><![CDATA[There is only one of each of these titles per server.]]></item>
 <item name="titles_get_h"><![CDATA[How do I get a title?]]></item>
 <item name="titles_get_p"><![CDATA[If you see a user with a title, you can blow their ship to smithereens to steal away the title. If you already have a title, your old title will be replaced and given to some alien. If you defeat an alien with a title, you'll also regain the title.]]></item>
 <item name="titles_lose_h"><![CDATA[Can I lose my title?]]></item>
 <item name="titles_lose_p"><![CDATA[Yes, if you're blown up by a NPC or a player, your title will be taken away and the NPC or enemy player will then fly around with your title. If another player destroys this NPC, they'll receive the title.<br />If you log out and remain offline for longer than 48 hours, your title will also be taken away and given to an alien. This way another user will have the opportunity to get a title. The time you spend in the NAZ also counts as offline time – so make sure to defend your title always: Defense is the best offense!]]></item>
 <item name="titles_info_h"><![CDATA[Can everyone see who holds the title at the moment?]]></item>
 <item name="titles_info_p"><![CDATA[Yes, you can drop by the Hall of Fame at any time to see who holds which title and how long they have held it for. In addition to that, you can also see who has held the title the longest. There is also a top 10 ranking for every title.]]></item>
 <item name="acknowledgement_h"><![CDATA[Recognition]]></item>
 <item name="acknowledgement_main_h"><![CDATA[This FAQ is based on the excellent work of]]></item>
 <item name="acknowledgement_main_p"><![CDATA[Bisco Brown<br />Mr. Flatout<br />Sow<br />Crystal Lion<br />f3ld<br />Sambagirl<br />KITWO<br />_section_<br />Fake<br />BPHorst<br />mblpz<br />--Patrick--Star--]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_h"><![CDATA[Galaxy gates]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_main_h"><![CDATA[What are galaxy gates?]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_main_p"><![CDATA[Galaxy gates are your gateway into strange new worlds. They are made of parts which are collected from the materializer. Once you've collected all the parts necessary for a galaxy gate, you can build one and fly into the face of danger. One small jump and you'll boldly be exploring a brand new world.<br /><br />With the materializer, you can build a variety of different jump gates.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_output_h"><![CDATA[What can I win from the materializer?]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_output_list_p"><![CDATA[You can receive the following items from the materializer:<br /><br />- Gate parts<br />- Elite Laser Ammo<br />- Elite Rockets and Mines<br />- Repair Voucher<br />- Xenomit<br />- Nanohull Strength<br /><br />There are no duds. Every click is a winner.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_output_duplicate_part_p"><![CDATA[If you win a gate part which you already have, you can use it as a multiplier in order to compound your winnings.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_output_repair_vouchers_p"><![CDATA[Repair credits will be used automatically the next time you repair your ship or drones.<br /><br />Premium members receive free repairs, meaning that their repair credits won't automatically be used to repair their ships.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_output_nanohull_p"><![CDATA[The Nanohull Strength is an energy reservoir for your ship that you can top off in the Galaxy Gate Materializer. It is a value that is independent of normal Hitpoints. If your ship gets damaged, your Nanohull Strength will be the first to dwindle. A yellow bar beneath your ship will show you how much Nanohull Strength you have left. Don't look back when flying into battle - you've never been this protected!]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_spins_h"><![CDATA[Can I carry out multiple materializer spins at once?]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_spins_main_p"><![CDATA[Yes. Thanks to the latest update, you can now carry out up to 100 materializer spins with one click.<br />Beneath the green materializer button, you will find a drop-down button showing the maximum number of materializer spins which can be carried out with one click of the button.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_spins_multiplier_p"><![CDATA[If extra energy is available, it will also automatically be used for this process.<br />The price of the selected number of materializer spins is shown directly on the button.<br />If during the materializer spin, the multiplier increases to x6, it will automatically be used entirely.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_pvemap_h"><![CDATA[How can I travel to new galaxies, and how can I leave them?]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_pvemap_main_p"><![CDATA[As soon as you've built a gate, your space adventure can begin. You can jump to a galaxy on the other side of the gate and start exploring the unknown world there. Take heed, you never know what's waiting for you on the other side. If you complete all the missions in this galaxy, you'll win awesome prizes.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_pvemap_leave_caption_p"><![CDATA[Requirements for leaving galaxy gate galaxies:]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_pvemap_leave_on_kill_p"><![CDATA[1. If you are shot down, your ship will be brought back to your home base for repair. You'll be able to keep the gate and return to this galaxy once again via a portal jump.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_pvemap_leave_after_wave_p"><![CDATA[2. If you've survived an NPC attack wave, you can select whether or not you want to return to the normal map through a gate or if you want to jump to the next map. If you leave the Galaxy Gate map, you can keep the gate and return to the map at a later point in time.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_pvemap_leave_after_completion_p"><![CDATA[3. If you master all galaxy gate challenges, you'll have something to be proud of! You'll be brought back to your home map and won't be able to return to the Galaxy Gate map. Should you want to return to this galaxy, you'll have to rebuild the gate.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_multiplier_h"><![CDATA[What can I do with a multiplier?]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_multiplier_main_p"><![CDATA[You can collect up to five multipliers and use them for galaxy gate spins.<br />- One multiplier = x2 winnings<br />- Two multipliers = x3 winnings<br />- Three multipliers = x4 winnings<br />- Four multipliers = x5 winnings<br />- Five multipliers = x6 winnings]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_multiplier_maximum_p"><![CDATA[If you've collected five multipliers, you'll win six times the given amount the next time you use the materializer!]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_multiplier_multilpier_on_parts_p"><![CDATA[If you use one or more multipliers for a galaxy gate spin and you win a new gate part, you won't get more of the same gate part, you'll win new parts for the gate. If you don't need that many parts to finish building your gate, then you'll receive ammo or Credits instead.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_costs_h"><![CDATA[How much does it cost to use materializer?]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_costs_main_p"><![CDATA[One galaxy gate spin costs 100 Uridium. Per spin, you can receive a gate part, 100 Uridium or other items. You can also win extra energy which will allow you to use the materializer for free.<br />The extra energy will be given to you as a daily bonus. Sometimes you can also find extra energy in bonus boxes.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_costs_discount_p"><![CDATA[If you are a Premium member and already have a rebate or Rebate Pack, these will be used as normal.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_hadesgate_h"><![CDATA[Can I play a galaxy gate with other pilots?]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_hadesgate_main_p"><![CDATA[Playing a galaxy gate with other pilots is only possible within the Hades Gate. Like all other gates, you must first build the Hades Gate in the Materializer for it to appear on your X-1 map. You can only enter it with a group of pilots and you must all be at the same stage. To make sure you’re at the same stage, look to the right of each group member’s name for the 1, 2 or 3 progress icon. Players’ progress is visible in the group window but only if they have built the Hades Gate. Lastly, all rewards won in the Hades Gate will be shared equally among group members.]]></item>
 <item name="galaxygates_caption_p"><![CDATA[<b>Greetings Space Pilots,</b><br /><br />Your spies stole a piece of top secret technology from the other companies' research labs: the galaxy gate materializer. Nothing like it has ever been seen before at DarkOrbit.<br /><br />With the help of the materializer, you can build many different jump portals to visit unknown galaxies and embark on new and dangerous challenges. If you complete all the challenges in a galaxy, you'll receive a huge reward.<br /><br />In addition to parts for the gates, you can also win repair credits, ammo and Xenomit. According to the first test results, the materializer is stable. Try it out now and rake in tons of prizes!<br /><br />]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_h"><![CDATA[CPUs]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_main_h"><![CDATA[What are CPUs?]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_main_p"><![CDATA[CPUs are helpful extras and extensions for your ship. They make fighting easier, provide you with more info about your opponent and allow you to manufacture special weapons.]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_fight_h"><![CDATA[Which CPUs are helpful in battle?]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_fight_p"><![CDATA[CPUs help you in battle by giving your weapons an extra boost, reducing your cool-down times or allowing you to use special weapon combinations.]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_boost_h"><![CDATA[Which CPUs strengthen the effect of my weapons?]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_boost_p"><![CDATA[Targeting Guidance CPUs such as AIM01 CPU and AIM02 CPU improve your chances of hitting a ship and reduce the rate of ship lasers missing the target.<br /><br /><i>AIM01 CPU</i> reduces the MISS rate by 25% and uses 10 Xenomit per volley.<br /><i>AIM02 CPU</i> reduces the MISS rate by 50% and uses 10 Xenomit per volley.<br /><br />Automatic weapon boost CPUs automatically upgrade lasers and rockets with raw materials from the lab.<br /><br /><i>NC AWB</i> boosts lasers and rockets with raw materials which are currently being used in the lab.<br /><i>NC AWR</i> only boosts rockets which are currently being used in the lab.<br /><i>NC AWL</i> only boosts lasers with raw materials which are currently being used in the lab.]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_cooldown_h"><![CDATA[Which CPUs reduce the cool-down time of my weapons?]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_cooldown_p"><![CDATA[The turbo rocket module and the Mine Turbo CPUs, MINT01 and MINT02, reduce the waiting time between firing rockets, laying mines or smart bombs or using Insta-shields.<br /><i>The turbo rocket module</i> doubles the firing speed of rocket launchers.<br /><i>MINT01 CPU</i> reduces both the cool-down time of mines and items made from mines by 25%.<br /><i>MINT02 CPU</i> reduces both the cool-down time of mines and items made from mines by 50%.]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_alternative_strategies_h"><![CDATA[Which CPUs allow special types of attacks?]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_alternative_strategies_p"><![CDATA[The AROL-X CPU, the SMB01 CPU and the ISH01 CPU allow alternative attack strategies to be used in battle.<br /><i>AROL-X</i> rapidly fires the selected type of rocket automatically for you during laser attacks.<br /><i>SMB01 CPU</i> creates an instant bomb out of 10 mines and 100 Xenomit, which explodes like a mine, but doesn't cause any damage to your ship.<br /><i>ISH01 CPU</i> provides you with protection for 3 seconds during enemy attacks. It uses up 10 mines and 100 Xenomit every time it is selected.<br /><br />The cool-down times for smart bombs and Insta-shields are the same as for mines.]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_extension_h"><![CDATA[Which CPUs upgrade existing functions?]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_extension_p"><![CDATA[Slot extension CPUs allow you to upgrade your ship's equipment. They increase the number of slots for special items in each configuration. Jump CPUs allow you to jump over neighboring maps. The Radar CPU shows you your current diplomacy status to others on the mini map.<br />The SL01 CPU creates 2 new slots, the SL02 CPU creates 4 new slots and the SL03 CPU creates 6 new slots for extras on board the ship. Only one Slot CPU can be used per configuration.<br /><i>JP01 CPU</i> lets you jump to the home map X-1, but only works to a maximum distance of map X-4 and NOT on PvP maps (4-X)! It's good for 10 jumps.<br /><i>JP02 CPU</i> lets you jump to the home map X-1 and works everywhere. It's good for 20 jumps. Only one Jump CPU can be used per configuration.<i>RD CPU</i> shows the overall diplomacy status on the mini map.]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_assistant_h"><![CDATA[Which CPUs protect you from unpleasant situations and help you make it through the game on a daily basis?]]></item>
 <item name="cpu_assistant_p"><![CDATA[The <i>Repair-bot auto CPU</i> automatically starts repairing robots if repair is needed and is able to be carried out.<br />The <i>AM CPU</i> automatically buys 10,000 rounds of laser ammunition in the event that you have less than 1,000 rounds on board your ship. Under settings you can specify the type of ammunition.<br />Drone repair CPUs fix your drones automatically if your ship has been destroyed.<br />The <i>DR01 CPU</i> repairs drones automatically when damage to your ship exceeds 70%, as long as you have enough Uridium available for the repairs. This CPU is good for 8 repairs.<br />The <i>DR02 CPU</i> repairs drones automatically when maximum damage has been done to your ship, as long as you have enough Uridium on board for the repairs. It is good for 32 repairs. One Drone-repair CPU can be used per configuration.<br />The Cloaking CPU <i>CL04K</i> allows you to cloak your ship 10 times up and remains in effect until you make an attack yourself.]]></item>
 <item name="booster_h"><![CDATA[Booster]]></item>
 <item name="booster_main_h"><![CDATA[What exactly are boosters?]]></item>
 <item name="booster_main_p"><![CDATA[Boosters give you the extra support you need to play better.<br />They boost/increase the value of your account or ship.<br />- Boosters can be <i>bought</i> for Uridium or <i>subscribed</i> to for a fee.<br />- Upon purchase, each booster is activated for a certain amount of time. Time will only be deducted on the space map.]]></item>
 <item name="booster_atglance_h"><![CDATA[What type of boosters are there?]]></item>
 <item name="booster_atglance_p"><![CDATA[<i>Experience booster</i><br />Gives you bonus EP.<br /><br /><i>Honor booster</i><br />Gives you bonus honor points.<br /><br /><i>Damage booster</i><br />Lets you cause extra damage.<br /><br /><i>Shield power booster</i><br />Increases your ship's maximum shield power.<br /><br /><i>Repair booster</i><br />Increases ship's repair speed.<br /><br /><i>Shield recharger booster</i><br />Increases shield's recharging speed.<br /><br /><i>Resource booster</i><br />Increases the amount of ore inside enemy cargo boxes.<br /><br /><i>Hit point booster</i><br />Increases ship's maximum HP limit.]]></item>
 <item name="booster_buywhere_h"><![CDATA[Where and how can I buy boosters?]]></item>
 <item name="booster_buywhere_p"><![CDATA[- Boosters can be bought in the <i>hangar</i>.<br />- Boosters can also be purchased in a <i>trading post auction</i>.]]></item>
 <item name="booster_buylimits_h"><![CDATA[How many boosters can I buy?]]></item>
 <item name="booster_buylimits_p"><![CDATA[- All booster types can used at the same time.<br />- As long as there is enough Uridium in your account, you can buy as many boosters as you want.<br />- If a booster is bought which is already active, the time for the booster which was just bought will be added to that of the old booster.]]></item>
 <item name="booster_active_h"><![CDATA[How can I see if a booster is active?]]></item>
 <item name="booster_active_p"><![CDATA[- If a booster is bought in the hangar, you'll be able to see if a booster is active and how much longer it is active for in its description.]]></item>
 <item name="booster_subscribe_h"><![CDATA[How can I subscribe to a booster?]]></item>
 <item name="booster_subscribe_p"><![CDATA[- If you have a subscription to a booster, a new booster will automatically be bought as soon as the active booster expires.<br />- The Uridium for the new booster will automatically be withdrawn from your game account.<br />- If you do not have enough Uridium at the time of withdrawal, your booster won't be extended. The subscription will remain in effect as long as it is not canceled by the user. As soon as there is enough Uridium in the account, the subscribed boosters will be automatically bought.]]></item>
 <item name="booster_unsubscribe_h"><![CDATA[How do I end my booster subscription?]]></item>
 <item name="booster_unsubscribe_p"><![CDATA[- You can cancel a booster subscription in the hangar by clicking on the <i>Cancel subscription</i> button in the booster's description.<br />- If a subscription is canceled, the booster which is active will remain active until it has expired, and a new one won't be bought afterwards.]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_h"><![CDATA[Summer Games]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_main_h"><![CDATA[What are the Summer Games?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_main_p"><![CDATA[The Summer Games are an annual event where space pilots from around the universe join together to crown the best of the best: the champion of all space pilots.<br />There's a new event every day to compete in. The goal here is to perform as best you can, grab the daily prize, and collect as many Championship points as possible. It's the only way for you to win the champion title for this year's Summer Games!]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_dailytasks_h"><![CDATA[What are daily events?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_dailytasks_p"><![CDATA[During the Summer Games, daily events will be held in which all users can compete for the daily award. The daily ranking will be determined by the points won during these events. At the end of the day, the player with the most points will be crowned the winner of the day. The daily winner and the best 99 players will be richly rewarded for their performances.<br /><br />Your 10 best placements from the daily events will be used at the end of the Summer Games to determine your championship ranking.]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_participate_h"><![CDATA[How can I compete in a daily event?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_participate_p" comment="&quot;abo beenden&quot; ist der Text mit dem Key booster_subscription_cancel aus der Datei resource.item.inc.php&#10;"><![CDATA[In order to compete in a daily event, you can take a look at the menu item <i>Summer Games</i> in the Mission area and accept these daily events just like you would for a normal mission.<br />If you've chosen to compete in an event, you'll see a counter appear on the space map which will show you your points.]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_cships_h"><![CDATA[What are the Summer Game Championships?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_cships_p"><![CDATA[The Summer Game Championships will take place throughout the course of the Summer Games. At the end of the event, a SG3 Champion will be determined.<br /><br />Championship points can be collected by competing in daily events. Only the 10 best daily results of each player will count towards the championship ranking. The player who collects the most "Championship points" throughout the course of the Summer Games will win the SG3 Championship and the title of the <i>SG3 Champion</i>.<br /><br />For an entire month, the champion will receive an indestructible drone #9 plus 50,000 Uridium.<br />Players who place 2nd to 100th will also be rewarded for their outstanding performances.]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_cships_participate_h"><![CDATA[How can I participate in the Summer Game Championships?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_cships_participate_p"><![CDATA[Every player who has started a daily event will automatically be entered into the Summer Game Championships.]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_viewranking_h"><![CDATA[Where can I take a look at my daily ranking and championship ranking?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_viewranking_p"><![CDATA[A detailed list of the ranking for daily events can be found in the corresponding menu in the Hall of Fame or on the "Summer Games" page in the quest area. You can see the championship ranking in the Hall of Fame by using the drop-down list.]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_bonuspoints_h"><![CDATA[How many bonus points are available for each type of ship?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_bonuspoints_p"><![CDATA[There are bonus points for some events if you use a weaker ship than the Goliath. The bonus points available are calculated using the following guidelines:<br /><br /> - Phoenix: 100% bonus<br /> - Yamato: 90% bonus<br /> - Leonov: 80%<br /> - Defcom: 70%<br /> - Liberator: 60%<br /> - Piranha: 50%<br /> - Nostromo: 40%<br /> - Vengeance: 20%<br /> - BigBoy: 10%]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_chances_h"><![CDATA[As a new player, do I even stand a chance of winning?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_chances_p"><![CDATA[It is generally much harder to win as a new player, and with a small ship, the conditions for winning the competition are much worse. That's why users with small ships will receive a bonus for the points they collect.]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_sideevents_h"><![CDATA[What other events are there?]]></item>
 <item name="summergames_sideevents_p"><![CDATA[Additional events will be held during the Summer Games 3 at different points in time, for example, Spaceball and Team Deathmatch (TDM). Every user can compete in these events. Just remember that these additional events will have no effect on your ranking for the Summer Games.]]></item>
</resource>
